let questionaire1 = [
    {
        question: "I am a great half-god, half-human king born from the union between a King and a goddess. I am a transcendent being so divine as to be two-thirds god and one-third human, and no others in the world could match me! Who am I?",
        answer: "Gilgamesh",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {	
        question: "I ruled the the city of Uruk during what time period?",
        answer: "between 2800 and 2500 BC",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Where was the city of Uruk?",
        answer: "Ancient Mesopotamia",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Where is my story recorded?",
        answer: "Epic of Gilgamesh",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "As the King of kings, the one who possessed everything in the world. What is my weapon of choice?",
        answer: "The Gate of Babylon",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire2 = [
    {
        question: "For political, personal gain, and vengence I founded the Order of Assassins. Who am I?",
        answer: "Hassan-i-Sabbah",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "What time period was I alive?",
        answer: "11th Century",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Where did I establish my Order?",
        answer: "Persia",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I wrote an autobiography when I was alive. Unfortunately, it would seem that it did not withstand the test of time... Currently, my autobiography is known the first part of an anonymous Isma'ili biography",
        answer: "Sargozasht-e Seyyedna",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I've been blessed with a divine miracle that which could swiftly and reliably bring death to its target. It's named after the Nineteen Angels of Hell in the Islamic Faith",
        answer: "Zabaniyya",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire3 = [
    {
        question: "I was greatest hero in Greece. I am a demi-god born from Zeus, the king of gods, and Alcmene, a human and wife of Amphitryon. I was the greatest hero in Freeze--a paragon of masculinity. Who am I?",
        answer: "Heracles",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "My most famous story consisted of twelve labors. When was this written?",
        answer: "Hellenistic Age",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Though my father is a god, I was born Earth. Where was I born?",
        answer: "Greece",
        isanswered: false
    },   
    {
        question: "There are many stories that tell the tale of my heroic adventures. What is my most notable table called?",
        answer: "Twelve Labours of Heracles",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "After completing my twelve labors I was blessed with an ability. What is this ability called?",
        answer: "God Hand: Twelve Labours",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire4 = [
    {
        question: "As a a poet and playwright from Elizabethan England, I wrote tragic plays which, till today, are heralded as one of the greatest plays ever written! Who am I?",
        answer: "William Shakespeare",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I was lucky to be born in a time period a cultural and artistic movement in England. What time period was this? ",
        answer: "English Renaissance",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Where was I born?",
        answer: "England",
        isanswered: false
    },   
    {
        question: "What is my greatest work?",
        answer: "Romeo and Juliet",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Published in 1623, my comedies, histories, and tragedies were compiled into a book. Today, scholars know this as what?",
        answer: "First Folio",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire5 = [
    {
        question: "I presided over the growth and decay of crops, bent the dragons and snakes to my will, and freely controlled the Garula familiars of the underworld. If the goddess of the harvest Ishtar was the Great Earth Mother that represented human life then I, who represented human death, was the Terrible Earth Mother. Who am I?",
        answer: "Ereshkigal",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: `The first myth that spoke of my tale was the epic poem "Inanna's Descent to the Underworld". This story was about the same time period as the "Epic of Gilgamesh". What was this time period called?`,
        answer: "2800 and 2500 BC",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "As the Queen of the Great Earth and goddess of Kur, where did I live?",
        answer: "In the land of the dead",
        isanswered: false
    },   
    {
        question: `Besides the epic poem "Inanna's Descent into the Underworld", there was another myth that told of my story. What was it called?`,
        answer: "Marriage to Nergal",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "My best move summons the punishment from the earth below to the world above! What is this move called?",
        answer: "Kur Kigal Irkalla",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire6 = [
    {
        question: "I was the king of the ancient Greek kingdom Macedon. After gaining generalship of Greece, I executed my late father's plan to conquer Persia. Who am I?",
        answer: "Alexander the Great",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I was King of Macedon, Pharaoh of Egypt, King of Persia, and Lord of Asia until what time period?",
        answer: "336 BC",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "Where did I spend most of my ruling years?",
        answer: "Asia and Northeast Africa",
        isanswered: false
    },   
    {
        question: "Accounts of my conquests are written in clay tablets. What is one of these clay tablets called?",
        answer: "Alexander Chronicle",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I have a large antique war chariot with two prows that is led by two Divine Bulls with rippling muscles. What is my chariot called?",
        answer: "Gordius Wheel",
        isanswered: false
    }
]

let questionaire7 = [
    {
        question: "Known as the son of king Arthur, but I'm actually a female. I was concieved through Morgan le Fay's witchraft and bound to always wear a helmet to conceal my identity.Through Morgan's recommendation I was accepted as one of the Knights of the Round Table. Who am I?",
        answer: "Mordred",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "I am part of someone's legend. What was the legend called?",
        answer: "Arthurian Legend",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: "As part of the Knights of the Round Table. Which nation did I spend the rest of my life?",
        answer: "Britannia",
        isanswered: false
    },   
    {
        question: "My story is based in part from a pseudohistorical account of British history. What was it called?",
        answer: "Historia Regum Britanniae",
        isanswered: false
    },
    {
        question: `Originally stored away by King Arthur in the armory of Camelot. Described as "more dazzling than any silver", it is an ornate, sparkling white silver sword adorned with splendid decorations, acting as a symbol of kingship denoting the right of succession of the throne. I stole this sword. What was it called?`,
        answer: "Clarent",
        isanswered: false
    }
]
